<resources>
    <string name="app_name">English Zubrila</string>
    <string name="les_s_start">Les\'s start!</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>

    <string name="text_english">" The modern world is becoming smaller all the time. Every day distances between different countries seem less. For this reason it's becoming more and more important to know different languages, especially English.
One billion people speak English today. That's about 20% of the world's population. 400 million people speak English as their first language. For the other 600 million people it's either a second language or a foreign language.
English is the first language in the United Kingdom, the United States of America, Australia and New Zealand. It is one of the official languages in Canada, the Irish Republic and the Republic of South Africa.
As a second language English is spoken in more than 60 countries. It is used by the government, businessmen and universities.
English is the language of politics and diplomacy, science and technology, business and trade, sport and pop music. 80% of all information in the world's computers is in English. 75% of the world's letters and faxes are in English. 60% of all international telephone calls are made in English. More than 60% of all scientific journals are written in English.
To know English today is absolutely necessary for every educated person, for every good specialist. Learning a language is not an easy thing. It's a long and slow process that takes a lot of time and patience. But it's a must.
English is taught throughout the world and a lot of people speak it quite well. In our country English is very popular: it is studied at schools (sometimes even at nursery schools), colleges and universities.
Everyone will speak English soon — I'm sure of it. We all need to understand each other. To do that we need an international language, and that's English.</string>

    <string name="text_rus">
Современный мир становится все меньше. Каждый день расстояния между различными странами кажется меньше. По этой причине становится все более и более важно знать различные языки, особенно английский.
Один миллиард человек говорит по-английски сегодня. Это около 20% населения мира. Для 400 миллионов людей английский язык- родной. Для остальных 600 миллионов людей это либо второй язык, либо иностранный язык.
Английский язык является первым языком в Соединенном Королевстве, Соединенных Штатах Америки, Австралии и Новой Зеландии. Это один из официальных языков в Канаде, Ирландской Республике и Южно Африканской Республике.
В качестве второго языка на английском говорят более чем в 60 странах. Он используется правительством, предпринимателями и университетами.
Английский - язык политики и дипломатии, науки и техники, бизнеса и торговли, спорта и поп-музыки. 80% всей информации в мире- на английском языке. 75% писем и факсов в мире- на английском языке. 60% всех международных телефонных звонков- на английском языке. Более 60% всех научных журналов- на английском языке.
Знать английский язык сегодня абсолютно необходимо для каждого образованного человека, для каждого хорошего специалиста. Изучение языка не является легким делом. Это долгий и медленный процесс, который отнимает много времени и терпения. Но это необходимо.
Английский язык преподается во всем мире и много людей говорят на нем очень хорошо. В нашей стране английский язык очень популярен: он изучается в школах (иногда даже в детских садах), колледжах и университетах.
Все будут говорить на английском языке скоро - я уверен в этом. Мы все должны понимать друг друга. Для этого нам нужен международный язык, и это - английский.</string>

</resources>

